Thank you for watching!
There's someone I want to talk to right now.
Continuing from the last episode, we will be discussing with Bananaman and the members on the topics they want to talk about.
We'll be bringing everyone even closer together.
I like to go on day trips to Japan.
A trip or a mini-trip.
Yes, like going to New Chitose Airport for two hours.
New Chitose is my destination.
The other day, I was in Osaka in less than three hours.
I don't know how far I can go.
If I have a day off, I'll check it out and go as far away as I can.
Chitose Airport is a great airport itself.
You can go from one end of the airport to the other, all the way up to the entrance of the international flights.
and see where you're going.
So that's what you're doing.
But it would be a waste of time.
It's a waste of time.
If you stay too long, you'll have too much time.
So I try to stay as close to the end as possible, like two and a half hours.
So I try to go as close to the end as possible, like two and a half hours, so that I can go home because I wanted to see a little more.
Why not a department store in Tokyo?
I like to go on rides, I guess.
So I was wondering if you could recommend a place to live for a day or something.
I was wondering if you have any recommendations for a place to live for a day, or for a place where one person can stay for a whole day.
I can't really do the whole thing by myself.
But you've been to a lot of places, haven't you, Mr. Himura?
No, I went to Mishima the other day.
I'd like to go to Mishima.
Mishima isn't far at all.
Mishima in Shizuoka Prefecture.
Mishima's on the Shinkansen.
I said, “Wow, 44 minutes, 44 minutes.
44 minutes from Tokyo Station on the Shinkansen.
From Shinagawa, maybe 37 minutes.
Wow!
And there's an eel restaurant called Sakuraya.
Go eat there, it's good.
I'll be back next time. Well, I'll be next.
I'm a gourmet, aren't I?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I went there, and it sure was a nice place.
There are people who go alone.
I don't go there alone.
Oh...
Tsutsui goes there too.
That's right.
Yes, he did.
Wow, all by himself.
I can't believe I'm going overseas by myself.
Aren't you worried?
I'm alone, so I don't have anyone to rely on.
I'm wondering if something accidental will happen.
It's fun to be excited.
You have that excitement.
Excitement is fun.
You don't seem like the type.
That's right.
You really don't.
It's like there's 15 of us.
No, actually, it's amazing.
It was a fight.
And there were a lot of other people who raised their hands.
A lot of people raised their hands.
A lot of hands.
Oh, Clovie.
But I wasn't traveling.
I've been to that beef bowl restaurant by myself.
Heh.
So you're all by yourself?
That's right.
Can you eat beef bowl by yourself?
Beef bowl by yourself, or churros at a university by yourself...
College churros by yourself? That's so small!
It works here too. The one that works here, too.
But that's exactly why Matsuo goes alone.
He even goes out to eat by himself.
I've been going to school alone since my junior year.
What happened?
You were there in the first year of high school?
But I'm fine by myself.
Do you go alone too?
I couldn't do anything by myself until last year, 2023.
But I set a goal for 2024 that I'll be able to do things by myself.
That's why I joined.
Yes, of course I can go to the café.
Cafe.
And recently I went to a music festival by myself.
That's pretty cool.
That's amazing.
It's like a live music club.
I didn't know what the system was, and I thought it was just a regular place with seats.
Standing?
Standing room, and I was all by myself.
I did it.
That's great.
But when you find an artist you like, you go all over the country by yourself.
That's true... you can travel.
Yes, yes, yes.
Who else raised their hand?
Lilia, are you an only child?
I'm an only child.
I used to play cards by myself.
This is a whole new world.
Tell me about it.
I love card games.
But I couldn't find anyone to play with.
So when I want to play cards by myself at home...
I'd have four seats set aside for a game of millionaires.
I love card games, too, but...
I like to erase my memory. You have to erase your memory.
You have to play the role of the person in this seat.
So it's a very serious game.
There's no “that seat over there has this card” or anything like that.
It's a serious game and fun.
That's a great story.
It's not scary.
So, for birthdays, you put a cake in the middle of the cake for four people, and you do it today.
You say, “Happy birthday,” and “Thank you.
It's just like that!
No, no, no. And I love speed.
I can't do it alone.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You have to stand in the middle, and you have to be ready here on the side, and you have to be able to get it out here.
I'm like, “You're right in the face.
It's a big deal if you do it all by yourself again.
You can do it over and over again.
Like, twice.
Like going to a baseball stadium.
It's hard to go to a baseball game alone, isn't it?
Yeah... you get to know the baseball fan next to you.
That's nice.
And since you're on social media, you want to take pictures, don't you?
In that case, can I ask the guy standing at the trash can to take a picture of me?
I'd rather take a picture with him than with the guy standing in the trash can.
Kakering's way of saying that.
I know how to say that with my current boss.
The cleaner.
Yes, that's right.
That's totally different.
Not at all. The guy standing at the dumpster.
Totally different.
Mr. Kakering.
What the hell are you doing?
Mr. Kakering. Mr. Kakering.
Okay, let's move on.
I joined Nogizaka when I was in middle school, so I've never had a part-time job.
I'm simply curious to know what kind of part-time jobs the members including Mr. Bananaman have had.
How many times did you say that? How many times did you say that? I did Denny's. You did Denny's? That's cool. I did it the first time I left here.
I remember how many times I said that. I did a Denny's when I was in high school, and then I did another one after I graduated.
I like it. Did you eat at Denny's? I did eat there. It's nice. And I've had part-time jobs.
I was a teacher at a private tutoring school. What do you teach? Tutoring third graders in Japanese.
No way! I can't do that.
I was so good I called the parents.
That was controversial too. Controversial? I wanted to call the parents and tell them that their grades were up, but I couldn't get the words out.
I couldn't find the words. The students were upset.
Then, about three days later, the most important person in the office, Yumiki-san, asked me if I'd like to work as a receptionist. He was like, “Yumiki, would you like to work at the reception desk?
So I had some problems as a lecturer I also worked part-time at a convenience store and at an izakaya
I also worked at a convenience store, an izakaya, and as an assistant at a cooking school.
When I went to a cooking class, I met a guy who was an assistant to the boss of the cooking class.
They're all like this because they're good communicators.
I guess everyone likes him. He was a shadow. Wow. Part-timer? Yes.
You're still doing that, right? I do it now, too.
I don't do it now, as expected.
There's a lot of them. I once lost a job at a tapioca shop.
Recently. A tapioca shop. Why did you fail? Because it was open and no one was there.
Why did you fail?
Oka? Shibata? Yes.
I joined Nogizaka at that time, but if I passed the audition, I couldn't work part-time.
So I got a part-time job as a concession stand girl at a ballpark.
You did? I did a little bit. Amazing.
What did you sell? Soft drinks.
Really? That's a lot of work.
Yes, it's heavy.
In the old days, the vendors would put a 1,000-yen bill on their finger here.
Like this, you put it in already
But after I quit, they went cashless. Everyone put a QR code here.
I see... I see...
You still used cash then?
I counted it, and I made mistakes, and I got scolded.
But some kind person offered to give it to me.
So many things happened. A lot happened, didn't it?
Okada? I was at Cafe Doutor.
Seriously? You're in Doutor? A girl like that?
About three months old? Three months, she's not even in the hood yet.
But I did.
You made Milano Sandwich A? Really?
That's amazing. I adore it.
Milano sandwich A. I've been eating Milano sandwich A for over 30 years.
I've been eating only “A” sandwiches.
I worked there.
I was a morning coffee guy, and my grandpa would come in every morning and ask for coffee.
He'd bring me chicken.
He told me to eat it.
I was too scared to eat it.
How did it end?
I thought it was going to end on a good note, but it made me feel bad, so I didn't eat it.
It doesn't matter that you didn't eat it.
Honest girl. She's an honest girl.
She's an honest girl.
What about your part-time job, Khaki?
I worked at a barbecue joint. Private.
A barbecue joint? Yes, sir.
You were a waiter?
And take orders?
Orders come in on a tablet.
I'd hand them the one that came in, and I'd say, “Here it is.
This table has this meat and that table has this meat.
And you brought it to them?
And then I'd bring it to them.
I wanted to put it in a draft beer mug and take it like this.
I wanted to do that, but...
But I'm too weak.
He's going to drink it?
Oh, my God, that girl.
He's too weak to hold a whole mug, it's so heavy.
Yeah, I'm not sure I could handle a whole bottle.
A beer this big, plus meat.
He's got something over here, too.I've got something over here.
With a mug like this.
I'm holding a mug and I'm holding meat and I'm going to say hello.
You say, “You never say hello.
I've never met him before, so I say hello.
I've never met you before, and all you say is, “Hello.
He says, “Excuse me.” He says, “Come in.
Yes, sir.
I couldn't handle heavy things, so I had to change nets and stuff.
Changing nets...
I didn't know they did that.
That's about it?
This way.
Okay, that's Yozi.
I did McDonald's in high school.
You really do McDonald's?
No, it's what you always wanted to do.
Terere, terere, terere.
What's that sound?
It's the sound of fries going up.
I can't make all kinds of fries!
I was a cashier.
So you do fries and drinks at the front?
Yes, I do it all by myself.
And the chicks?
Fries.
She enjoys it.
That kind of thing.
Definitely... like making them.
I used to date a guy in high school who worked at MacDonald's.
Oh, yeah?
I'm pretty much the best at dating Macs. Yeah, in my hometown... they opened the first Mac when I was in high school.
You had to go to Ikebukuro to get one.
I caught up with a guy 5 years older than me who worked there. He drove a Silvia.
But he was a big guy with a navy blue uniform, a Nissan Silvia.
I had a crush on a grown woman back then. The waitress at the McDonald's was five years older than me.
How did you know her? At the fair?
It wasn't a festival. It wasn't a festival. It was a friend of mine who knew her. It's not a festival. It's not a festival. It's just that my friend knew him.
A friend's acquaintance. Mac's is kind of a long time ago.
So, Mr. Yoshida, did you ever go through the drive-thru? Oh, I helped out once.
I'm a left hander.
I drive on the left side of the road.
McDonald's is far away. You always like Big Macs here.
I always like Big Macs here. I can't hear you.
I got help once. Can't you hear me? I'll just have to take a long tube with me.
Big Mac Grover.
Let's read Mac.
Cocosco Chateraise.
It's still coming out.
Secret story of my part-time job as an amateur
I serve food at hotels for banquets, receptions, wedding receptions, etc.
At the time it was fine.
I don't know when I started spilling.
But I did have a little run in once at a good friend's house or something.
And what about fate?
I'm going to Cocos.
Cocos.
Cocos and Chateraise.
Chateraise? Are you serious?
I used to do that.
I used to write my name on cakes with a chocolate pen.
But a few weeks after I started working there, they asked me to write “Overseer” in kanji characters.
A chocolate message.
Yes, I had to write my name on the name plate with a chocolate pen.
But it's too difficult.
Director, that's super hard!
Can't I just write in katakana?
It didn't work.
But...
I was crushed.
It was a lot of work.
Are Cocos and Chateraise taking the high road?
We did.
Coco's is that hamburger place.
Yes, the hamburger steak. That's right, a hamburger steak wrapped in a wrapper.
It's like a little iron stone.
That's right, that's right.
That's the part where you grill it.
That's nice, isn't it?
With about five griddles.
Really? Was it good?
It was good.
It's a big plum.
What do you think?
I'll see what I can do.
That's Akko's way of messing with you.
Yoda, did he do it?
Yes, he did.
You're kidding me, Yoda.
I've wanted to ride since I was about 8 years old.
I was 16 and a freshman in high school.
I'd also like to climb a tree and watch over the kids so they don't fall out.
What's with the part-time job?
Where's the bosu?
What's that job?
I get about 1,000 yen.
Wow!
But I once saved a man's life
I saved a man's life once.
Really?
You fell?
I fell.
I was watching him, thinking he was about to fall.
And then he fell.
It hit my head.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
I was fine.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. I'm here.
It's here.
I knew you'd fall for it.
Oh, my God, he's working part-time.
Oh, my God.
Okay, next move.
Kubo.
Sorry about that.
I've always wondered how you sleep.
I need 7 hours of sleep.
My body can move most efficiently on 7 hours of sleep.
Well, they say it's better to sleep that much.
What time do people go to bed and how many hours of sleep do they get?
Well, Stella-san, for example, gets up in the morning, so...
What time do you usually go to bed and wake up?
I can't decide anymore.
I can't decide.
I get sick if I try to force myself to sleep.
I can't sleep.
So I've decided to go to sleep when I feel sleepy.
I might have said this, too.
Now that the no-stop has started...
So now, at 1:00 or 2:00 in the morning, for example, around that time...
If I say I'm into Stranger Things, I'll watch it until, like, 4:00 in the morning.
And then I'll watch parts of the show the next day, and I'll think about what I'm going to do.
I'll put up a bunch of stuff when I can't get up to prevent a lot of things.
Kimura-san already knows what he's going to do, so he goes to bed rather early.
I'm in bed as early as 9:00 a.m.
But it rarely goes beyond today.
Especially now.
So you're right.
I wake up at 4:00 or 5:00.
Like today.
Grandpa's.
Yeah.
What time does everyone go to bed?
Even I'm in bed by midnight. Even I'm in bed by midnight.
You decided to go to bed?
Yes, that's right.
Do you wake up at a certain time?
I usually wake up around 7:00.
Seven o'clock.
It's a good life.
What about you, Endo?
I'm like Shitara... I don't decide.
I don't decide anymore.
I sleep when I'm sleepy.
If I can't sleep, I can't sleep.
I also sleep when I'm on the move.
Yes, I sleep when I'm on the move and I feel sleepy.
People who can't sleep can't sleep, even if they try.
What about Miyamoto?
I'm the unhealthiest one in the group.
I can't sleep until 5 a.m.
Still?
Yes, I still do.
My hobby is gaming.
My gaming friends live around that time.
What do you do when you have to work early?
I don't sleep.
I know... people like that... who go without sleep.
I'm the same way... if I have to be on location early, I go without sleep.
What time do you go?
I don't really decide. I like the middle of the night best.
So basically around 3:00 or 4:00.
Everyone sleeps pretty late.
It's really important for beauty.
They say that's the golden hour.
I ate a lot of tomatoes.
So it's all right.
If you don't sleep, you don't produce anything, you know, that substance.
That's why you look so beautiful.
It's true.
I'm sure. I'm sure.
I'm telling the truth.
It's true!
Relay!
I can never sleep without silence.
I know.
When it's really silent, the smallest sound makes me nervous and bothered.
I usually build a fire and...
Visuals?
Yes, with sound.
Don't you sleep with the fire burning?
The crackling sound?
But it's a natural sound?
Yes, it is.
I like bonfires and watching video games.
I sleep with either a bonfire or the sound of gunfire.
Gunfire?
That's extreme.
But if there's no sound...
I can't sleep without sound.
Saugu.
I try to go to bed at 11:00 or so.
It's early.
I have to have a routine before I go to bed or I'll feel sick.
With the routine?
Flexibility first.
Really? I'm not lying.
Seriously, you really do that?
You put some oil on it, take five breaths, and then you just naturally fall asleep.
What the hell is that?
I've heard of people who do that, but it's really true.
I couldn't sleep if I didn't do that even on the day of the concert.
So I've turned to that.
I can sleep the whole day if I want to.
The night before a holiday, I thought I'd stay up a little later.
But around 9:00 or 10:00, I felt sleepy.
I thought to myself, “It's my day off already. It's my day off, and I'm thinking...
I slept till noon and went to bed the next day.
I woke up in the afternoon and ate a bowl of eel.
Then my blood sugar rises, I get sleepy again, and I sleep until the evening.
Then I took a shower.
I ate natto rice and the rest of the eel.
and slept again until the next morning.
That's amazing!
I usually wonder what time I'd go to bed if I wasn't on vacation or something.
I wake up 15 minutes before I go to work.
Fifteen minutes before.
I put on my next outfit, go to bed, wash my face, and go.
Amazing!
I'll teach you Captain Umezawa's revolutionary method of waking up early.
Chromia.
I can't decide what to do.
Before I go to bed, I have to study for the next day's baseball game.
I have to finish everything before I go to bed.
I try to finish until midnight or so before going to bed.
This is great, but
I haven't been doing it recently.
For example, when I get a job for a play or something...
I guess I'm already a worrier.
I do it over and over again.
At home.
I hate it.
I can't sleep because of it.
So in the future...
If they have to do it all in advance.
They don't want to do anything right.
I started this job.
I'm saying all the right things every morning.
They feel like they have to do something.
So be careful.
I'll be careful.
Did you moderate?
I'll sleep in moderation.
I'll be fine. It's okay.
I guess everyone's up pretty late at night.
I was surprised...
Mr. Umezawa...
I asked him when he goes to bed.
He said around 3:00 a.m.
Baba! Baba! Like that.
Around 3:00.
He seems so tight-assed.
You're always so visual.
He's always so energetic.
You're a perfect human being.
I didn't expect him to stay up that late.
I was so surprised.
I don't make up my mind at night.
I'm confident I won't oversleep.
There you go.
I can't get up.
But when I was doing the morning show for a year or so.
I had to wake up at 2:30 in the morning, and there was a way to make sure I could get up.
There is no such thing. No, there is. I was often asked for advice.
Before I go to bed, I put my mind to it.
Mentalism, mentalism, mentalism... There's absolutely no such thing.
You should try it today. You'll be amazed at what you can do.
Before you go to bed, if you have to get up at 6:00 a.m. tomorrow, get up at 6:00 a.m., get up at 6:00 a.m.
You don't have to wake up with that, but you can wake up with it.
I can respond to it. My brain is probably more sensitive to the sound of the alarm because I have to get up at 6:00.
You can't do that if you're a person who can't wake up, because you don't put that sense of urgency and energy into it.
You're full of it.
Yes, I see... but I get sleepy during long programs.
If you press this point, I'll do it and chew the tip of the tongue.
You should go to bed. I don't feel sleepy now.
I've got free time, what shall I do?
What do you want me to do?
We were just talking.
But sometimes it's nice... to talk about how I'm more of a thinker... about what made you happiest... when you heard that.
I'll do something like that next time.
Manatsu no Zenkoku Tour mobile selection starts today! Zero calories for a nighttime meal while watching NogizakaManatsu no Zenkoku Tour Mobile Selection Starts Today Zero Calories for a Night Meal While Watching Nogizaka
Next time: Iikero festival!
I'm Kaede Sato, and I'm going to play “Goo” at first
Janken (rock-paper-scissors-scissors) pawn
Whoever wins will have a good week starting tomorrow Please subscribe to our channel!